Tokarzewski-Karaszewicz, Jan. Papers, 1895-1955 (inclusive), 1918-1954 (bulk): A Finding Aid.
Papers, 1895-1955 (inclusive), 1918-1954 (bulk).
- I. Correspondence
  - H-O ([Box 2])
    - V-W 1919-1952, [Box 4, Folder 35].
      - Vasylko, Mykola (1868-1924; Diplomat, parliamentarian, and Bukovynian civic figure; ambassador of the UNR in Switzerland and Germany), 1921-1922
      - Vatchnadzé, Data (Vahnadze), 1928-1942
      - Villari, Luigi (1876-), 1949-1950
      - Vittori, Beata, 1950
      - Volborth, Carl Alexander von, 1952
      - Warren, Derek E., n.d.
      - [Warsquiel, Jerry de], n.d.
      - Webster, Nesta Helen, 1949-1952
      - Weryha, Alesander, 1946-1952
      - Wiedner, H. von, 1952
      - Wieliczka, Z., 1940
      - [Wielkopolski, B.], 1954
      - Wielhorski, Wladyslaw, 1932
      - [Wienilowski], 1943
      - Wierer, Rudolf, 1953
      - Willebois, Frieda de, 1919
      - [Wrassprbocky], 1936-1937
    - Z 1942-1943, 1952-1954, [Box 4, Folder 36].
      - Zabins, Zofia, 1952-1953
      - Zagoiski, A., 1953
      - Zalototskyi, Andrei, 1954
      - Zappala' Nicolosi, Gr. Uff. Nob. Vito, 1943
      - Zeiger, I.A., 1942
      - unidentified [Anka], 1949-1954
      - unidentified--misc., 1919-1953
- II. Subject files
  - A-I ([Box 4])
    - unidentified [Anka], 1949-1954, [Box 4, Folder 37].
    - unidentified, 1919-1953, [Box 4, Folder 38].
    - Black Sea Alliance,1921-1922, [Box 4, Folder 39].
    - Catholic dignitories (Correspondence), 1918-1937, [Box 4, Folder 40].
    - Ukrainian Citizenship Law, 1918, [Box 4, Folder 41].
    - East European Problem (Black Sea), 1921-1922, [Box 4, Folder 42].
    - Famine in Ukraine, 1933, [Box 4, Folder 43].
    - Proclamation of independence of Georgia, [Box 4, Folder 44].
    - Correspondence in matters of the Legation in Constantinople - 1919-1921, [Box 4, Folder 45].
    - Legation in Constantinople - Correspondence in Financial Matters - 1920-1922, [Box 4, Folder 46].
    - Legation in Constantinople - 1919-1923, [Box 4, Folder 47].
    - Ukrainian Legation in Constantinople - Report - Jan. 1979 - March 1920, [Box 4, Folder 48].
    - Constantinople - Misc., [Box 4, Folder 49].
  - K-Z ([Box 5])
    - Knights of Malta, 1918-1945, [Box 5, Folder 50].
    - Orders (Correspondence), 1920, 1935-1938, 1948, [Box 5, Folder 51].
    - Riga Peace Treaty, March 18, 1921, [Box 5, Folder 52].
    - Saint George affair, Order of, 1934-1936, [Box 5, Folder 53].
    - Schwartzbart process, 1927, [Box 5, Folder 54].
    - Manifest of Hetman Skoropadsky - Nov. 14, 1918, [Box 5, Folder 55].
    - Turkey, Statutes of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, n.d., [Box 5, Folder 56].
    - Subject files: Ukrainian Academic Committee,1926-1932, [Box 5, Folder 57].
    - Statutes of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs and other Institutions, 1918-1924, [Box 5, Folder 58].
    - Ukrainian Organizations in Great Britain, 1953-1954, [Box 5, Folder 59].
- III. Writings ([Boxes 6, 7,8, 9, 10])
  - Articles (Manuscripts), 1932-1952, [Box 6, Folder 60].
  - Articles (Manuscripts), n.d., [Box 6, Folder 61].
  - Articles (Manuscripts), n.d., [Box 6, Folder 62].
  - Articles (Manuscripts.)--Konstytutsiina istoriia Ukrainy (Bks. I-IV), n.d., [Box 6, Folder 63].
  - Articles (Manuskripts)--Konstytutsiina istoriia Ukrainy (Bks. V-X), n.d., [Box 6, Folder 64].
  - Articles (Manuscripts)--Lototska-Tokarzewski, Oksana, n.d., [Box 6, Folder 65].
  - Articles (Published), 1923-1937, [Box 7, Folder 66].
  - Articles (Published), 1941-1952, [Box 7, Folder 67].
  - Articles (Published), 1953-1954, [Box 7, Folder 68].
  - Articles (Published)--Konstytutsiina istoriia Ukrainy, 1961, [Box 7, Folder 69].
  - Articles (Published)--Lototska-Tokarzewski, Oksana,1933-1951, [Box 7, Folder 70].
  - Bibliographical notes, [Box 7, Folder 71].
  - Heraldic research, n.d, [Box 8, Folder 72].
  - Heraldic research, n.d., [Box 8, Folder 73].
  - Heraldic research, n.d., [Box 8, Folder 74].
  - Heraldic research, n.d., [Box 8, Folder 75].
  - Heraldic research, n.d., [Box 9, Folder 76].
  - Heraldic research, n.d., [Box 9, Folder 77].
  - Clippings - 1926-1954, [Box 9, Folder 78].
  - Correspondence re: residency, 1947-1952, [Box 9, Folder 79].
  - Documents: 1895, 1906-1919, [Box 9, Folder 80].
  - Documents, 1920-1930, [Box 9, Folder 81].
  - Documents, 1931-1937, [Box 9, Folder 82].
  - Documents, 1940-1948, [Box 10, Folder 83].
  - Heraldry, n.d., [Box 10, Folder 84].
  - Identifications (passports, etc.), [Box 10, Folder 85].
  - Letterheads & cards, n.d., [Box 10, Folder 86].
  - Literature, n.d., [Box 10, Folder 87].
- IV. Personal files ([Boxes 11, 12, 13, 14])
  - Photographs ([Box 11, Folder 88])
  - Pictures, n.d. ([Box 11, Folder 89])
  - Photographs (Album), n.d. ([Box 11, Folder 90])
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. ([Box 11, Folder 91])
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. ([Box 11, Folder 92])
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. ([Box 11, Folder 93])
  - Photographs, n.d. ([Box 12, Folder 94])
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. ([Box 12, Folder 95])
  - Miscellaneous, n.d. ([Box 12, Folder 96])
  - Miscellaneous (Varia), n.d. ([Box 12, Folder 97])
  - Pins, badges, stamps, icons, and notebooks ([Box 13])
  - Pins, pipes, and seals ([Box 14])